# Thuthukani Khumalo

Johannesburg Metropolitan Area

kthuthukani4@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/thuthukani-khumalo-5a259719b

## Summary

I'm a tech enthusiast, with a keen interest in helping businesses solve problems using technology. I'm interested in a career in technology because it provides an opportunity to combine my analytical and creative skills.

My frustration of using buggy software fuelled my passion to specialise in Quality Assurance testing, my motivation in QA is driven by the serious implications of a software bug in different industries.

I'm versatile, flexible and a collaborative team player. Dedicated to improve my skills.

I'm able to work independently and as a team member.

I'm curious, investigative and pay attention to detail.

## **Experience**



## **Marketing Specialist**

Centrax Systems

Aug 2020 - Feb 2021 (7 months)

created content for social media platforms, mostly images and videos. I was part of the team that focuses on the design and copywrite for the companies products and services. Strategizing and planning for social media campaigns. Create and design wireframes, workflow and user interface for websites and mobile application.



## Digital Content Associate

Cape Innovation and Technology Initiative (CiTi)

Dec 2019 - Nov 2020 (1 year)

Learned design front-end website using HTML5 ,CSS and Javascript. Writing blogs for social media, research and analysis

### Education



#### WeThinkCode

NQF Level 5, Information Technology(Systems development)

Sep 2021 - Dec 2022

#### Davis&Dean

**Business Administration** Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

#### MH Joosub Technical School

NQF Level 4

## **Licenses & Certifications**

- **Growth mindset** Gnowbe
- Professionalism Gnowbe
- **Time Management** Gnowbe
- **<u>communication</u>** Gnowbe
- **<u>d</u>** Teamwork Gnowbe
- Problem Solving & Critical Thinking Gnowbe
- An Introduction to Zoho CRM Zoho
- Managing Projects Davis&Dean 13499
- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Grow with Google Africa 5ZCF3CYXC
- Absa Yes For Youth Program Digital Associate Capaciti
- Java(Basic) Certificate HackerRank 0FF256131979
- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp

## **Skills**

Java • Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • C# • .NET Core • NUnit • Teamwork • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • HTML5 • Communication